{
    "id": "caac3eec2dee43cc80df2cba40e82e00",
    "title": "Should or Would | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Everybody ............................. wear seat belts.",
            "description": "We use should to talk about obligation. Would is not possible with this meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "39e26a49bd56431faa4439e3d6af0b0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "When we were kids, we ................................ spend hours playing football.",
            "description": "To talk about past habits, we use 'would'.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "178f6b8416cb40e889db22587ab42c30"
        },
        {
            "question": "I told them we ................................ probably be late.",
            "description": "In British English, with the first person pronouns I and we both would and should can be used to express simple futurity. Note that should is not normally used with this meaning in American English. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2f5812a332fc4528a9de1ed931ddf2a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ................................ be grateful for an early reply.",
            "description": "In British English, with the first person pronouns I and we both would and should can be used to express simple futurity. Note that should is not normally used with this meaning in American English. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6c221a4d6514416fab91d27f8a4dbb39"
        },
        {
            "question": "People ............................... drive more carefully.",
            "description": "To express obligation, we use should.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d44cf8023ff6452f95017056b9ead51b"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................ you like something to eat?",
            "description": "In polite offers and requests, we use 'would', not 'should'.",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b4dce7d68a5441a481f6e71eb0b665b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................... we invite Mary?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Should",
                "Would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bed27362378d4061a3ff439153c3d6e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ............................... not have called him a fool - it really upset him.",
            "description": "We use 'should not have ' to refer to unwanted things that happened. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b2de49dc72f146f4a453049ed628b64b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I knew that I ............................ write to her, but it seemed too difficult.",
            "description": "We use 'should' to talk about obligations. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8802704a3bcd48e98e794b3e16674b02"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. we call the police?",
            "description": "In questions, should is used to ask for advice or instructions. ",
            "answers": [
                "Should",
                "Would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2dccfab0ac9a4d0fba0b9b23f6096d5e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you ................................... behave like this?",
            "description": "We use 'wish + would' to express ideas such as dissatisfaction or irritation. ",
            "answers": [
                "wouldn't",
                "shouldn't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f3098798dad64991815ab1749db5d25e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish it ............................. stop raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4867023965f949d4a441e709946ada23"
        }
    ]
}